[{ "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 1, "anagramsQuestionText": "DORMITORY", "anagramsAnswerText": "DIRTY ROOM", "gamesGameId": 1, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 1, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 2, "anagramsQuestionText": "DICTIONARY", "anagramsAnswerText": "INDICATORY", "gamesGameId": 2, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 2, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 3, "anagramsQuestionText": "SCHOOLMASTER", "anagramsAnswerText": "THE CLASSROOM", "gamesGameId": 3, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 3, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 4, "anagramsQuestionText": "ELVIS", "anagramsAnswerText": "LIVES", "gamesGameId": 4, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 4, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 5, "anagramsQuestionText": "LISTEN", "anagramsAnswerText": "SILENT", "gamesGameId": 5, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 5, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 6, "anagramsQuestionText": "MADAM CURIE", "anagramsAnswerText": "RADIUM CAME", "gamesGameId": 6, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 6, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 7, "anagramsQuestionText": "POSTMASTER", "anagramsAnswerText": "STAMP STORE", "gamesGameId": 7, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 7, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 8, "anagramsQuestionText": "A TELESCOPE", "anagramsAnswerText": "TO SEE PLACE", "gamesGameId": 8, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 8, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 9, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE EYES", "anagramsAnswerText": "THEY SEE", "gamesGameId": 9, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 9, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 10, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE EARS", "anagramsAnswerText": "HEAR SET", "gamesGameId": 10, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 10, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 11, "anagramsQuestionText": "DESPERATION", "anagramsAnswerText": "A ROPE ENDS IT", "gamesGameId": 11, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 11, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 12, "anagramsQuestionText": "CONVERSATION", "anagramsAnswerText": "VOICES RANT ON", "gamesGameId": 12, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 12, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 13, "anagramsQuestionText": "BUTTERFLY", "anagramsAnswerText": "FLUTTER BY", "gamesGameId": 13, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 13, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 14, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE HILTON", "anagramsAnswerText": "HINT HOTEL", "gamesGameId": 14, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 14, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 15, "anagramsQuestionText": "SOFTWARE", "anagramsAnswerText": "SWEAR OFT", "gamesGameId": 15, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 15, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 16, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE DETECTIVES", "anagramsAnswerText": "DETECT THIEVES", "gamesGameId": 16, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 16, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 17, "anagramsQuestionText": "SEMOLINA", "anagramsAnswerText": "IS NO MEAL", "gamesGameId": 17, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 17, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 18, "anagramsQuestionText": "PRESBYTERIANS", "anagramsAnswerText": "BEST IN PRAYERS", "gamesGameId": 18, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 18, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 19, "anagramsQuestionText": "MARTIN SCORSESE", "anagramsAnswerText": "SCREEN IS A STORM", "gamesGameId": 19, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 19, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 20, "anagramsQuestionText": "BARBIE DOLL", "anagramsAnswerText": "LIBERAL BOD", "gamesGameId": 20, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 20, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 21, "anagramsQuestionText": "ELEVEN PLUS TWO", "anagramsAnswerText": "TWELVE PLUS ONE", "gamesGameId": 21, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 21, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 22, "anagramsQuestionText": "MEL GIBSON", "anagramsAnswerText": "BONG SMILE", "gamesGameId": 22, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 22, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 23, "anagramsQuestionText": "ADMIRER", "anagramsAnswerText": "MARRIED", "gamesGameId": 23, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 23, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 24, "anagramsQuestionText": "CONTRADICTION", "anagramsAnswerText": "ACCORD NOT IN IT", "gamesGameId": 24, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 24, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 25, "anagramsQuestionText": "DEBIT CARD", "anagramsAnswerText": "BAD CREDIT", "gamesGameId": 25, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 25, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 26, "anagramsQuestionText": "NATURALIST", "anagramsAnswerText": "A TRAILS NUT", "gamesGameId": 26, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 26, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 27, "anagramsQuestionText": "BASIC", "anagramsAnswerText": "IS ABC", "gamesGameId": 27, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 27, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 28, "anagramsQuestionText": "HOT WATER", "anagramsAnswerText": "WORTH TEA", "gamesGameId": 28, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 28, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 29, "anagramsQuestionText": "A PALINDROME", "anagramsAnswerText": "DIPOLAR NAME", "gamesGameId": 29, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 29, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 30, "anagramsQuestionText": "ENOUGH", "anagramsAnswerText": "HUGE NO", "gamesGameId": 30, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 30, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 31, "anagramsQuestionText": "ALIBI", "anagramsAnswerText": "I BAIL", "gamesGameId": 31, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 31, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 32, "anagramsQuestionText": "OSCAR STATUE", "anagramsAnswerText": "TO ACE US STAR", "gamesGameId": 32, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 32, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 33, "anagramsQuestionText": "LAST WISH", "anagramsAnswerText": "WITH LASS", "gamesGameId": 33, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 33, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 34, "anagramsQuestionText": "OLYMPIAD", "anagramsAnswerText": "I DO MY LAP", "gamesGameId": 34, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 34, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 35, "anagramsQuestionText": "WAITRESSES", "anagramsAnswerText": "ER WE ASSIST", "gamesGameId": 35, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 35, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 36, "anagramsQuestionText": "PARODIST", "anagramsAnswerText": "I DO PARTS", "gamesGameId": 36, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 36, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 37, "anagramsQuestionText": "ACTOR ROBIN WILLIAMS", "anagramsAnswerText": "CLOWN OR A BIT SIMILAR", "gamesGameId": 37, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 37, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 38, "anagramsQuestionText": "GREENWICH STATION", "anagramsAnswerText": "WHENCE I GOT TRAINS", "gamesGameId": 38, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 38, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 39, "anagramsQuestionText": "CONFESSIONAL", "anagramsAnswerText": "ON SCALE OF SIN", "gamesGameId": 39, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 39, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 40, "anagramsQuestionText": "ACTRESS MARIA SCHNEIDER", "anagramsAnswerText": "DAME IS A RICH SCREEN STAR", "gamesGameId": 40, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 40, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 41, "anagramsQuestionText": "BRITISH AIRWAYS", "anagramsAnswerText": "BRITS IRISH AWAY", "gamesGameId": 41, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 41, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 42, "anagramsQuestionText": "A SOMERSAULT", "anagramsAnswerText": "USE ARMS A LOT", "gamesGameId": 42, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 42, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 43, "anagramsQuestionText": "MOTHER IN LAW", "anagramsAnswerText": "WOMAN HITLER", "gamesGameId": 43, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 43, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 44, "anagramsQuestionText": "FATHER IN LAW", "anagramsAnswerText": "NEAR HALFWIT", "gamesGameId": 44, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 44, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 45, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE CUBAN CIGARS", "anagramsAnswerText": "THUS A BIG CANCER", "gamesGameId": 45, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 45, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 46, "anagramsQuestionText": "PARADISE", "anagramsAnswerText": "A PRAISED", "gamesGameId": 46, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 46, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 47, "anagramsQuestionText": "GREAT CITY OF LONDON", "anagramsAnswerText": "ROOT CITY OF ENGLAND", "gamesGameId": 47, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 47, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 48, "anagramsQuestionText": "MIDEAST", "anagramsAnswerText": "MAD SITE", "gamesGameId": 48, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 48, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 49, "anagramsQuestionText": "ESPANIOL", "anagramsAnswerText": "OLE SPAIN", "gamesGameId": 49, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 49, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 50, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE ASIAN", "anagramsAnswerText": "AH IN EAST", "gamesGameId": 50, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 50, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 51, "anagramsQuestionText": "SUICIDES", "anagramsAnswerText": "CUSS I DIE", "gamesGameId": 51, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 51, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 52, "anagramsQuestionText": "GODLESS DOLLAR", "anagramsAnswerText": "A LORDLESS GOLD", "gamesGameId": 52, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 52, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 53, "anagramsQuestionText": "CONFITURE", "anagramsAnswerText": "ONCE FRUIT", "gamesGameId": 53, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 53, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 54, "anagramsQuestionText": "LIVRES", "anagramsAnswerText": "SILVER", "gamesGameId": 54, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 54, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 55, "anagramsQuestionText": "HIS HAREM", "anagramsAnswerText": "SHARE HIM", "gamesGameId": 55, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 55, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 56, "anagramsQuestionText": "REAL SEX", "anagramsAnswerText": "RELAXES", "gamesGameId": 56, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 56, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 57, "anagramsQuestionText": "VERTIGO", "anagramsAnswerText": "I GOT REV", "gamesGameId": 57, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 57, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 58, "anagramsQuestionText": "OLIGARCH", "anagramsAnswerText": "A RICH LOG", "gamesGameId": 58, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 58, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 59, "anagramsQuestionText": "A PRESCIENT", "anagramsAnswerText": "CAN SEE TRIP", "gamesGameId": 59, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 59, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 60, "anagramsQuestionText": "SATISFACTION", "anagramsAnswerText": "I SO FANTASTIC", "gamesGameId": 60, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 60, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 61, "anagramsQuestionText": "GOLDEN MEDAL", "anagramsAnswerText": "MOLD A LEGEND", "gamesGameId": 61, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 61, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 62, "anagramsQuestionText": "A SPAGHETTI", "anagramsAnswerText": "HI GET PASTA", "gamesGameId": 62, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 62, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 63, "anagramsQuestionText": "BARGAIN", "anagramsAnswerText": "A GRAB IN", "gamesGameId": 63, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 63, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 64, "anagramsQuestionText": "ECONOMY", "anagramsAnswerText": "MONEY CO", "gamesGameId": 64, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 64, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 65, "anagramsQuestionText": "ADORE", "anagramsAnswerText": "O DEAR", "gamesGameId": 65, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 65, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 66, "anagramsQuestionText": "AGAIN", "anagramsAnswerText": "I A NAG", "gamesGameId": 66, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 66, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 67, "anagramsQuestionText": "PERVERSITY", "anagramsAnswerText": "IS VERY PERT", "gamesGameId": 67, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 67, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 68, "anagramsQuestionText": "CHOLESTEROL", "anagramsAnswerText": "CELL SHOOTER", "gamesGameId": 68, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 68, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 69, "anagramsQuestionText": "CONFIRMED", "anagramsAnswerText": "MIND FORCE", "gamesGameId": 69, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 69, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 70, "anagramsQuestionText": "A MOTHER", "anagramsAnswerText": "THE AMOR", "gamesGameId": 70, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 70, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 71, "anagramsQuestionText": "VIETNAMESE", "anagramsAnswerText": "SEEM NATIVE", "gamesGameId": 71, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 71, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 72, "anagramsQuestionText": "RENAULT", "anagramsAnswerText": "REAL NUT", "gamesGameId": 72, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 72, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 73, "anagramsQuestionText": "FANATICISM", "anagramsAnswerText": "FIT MANIACS", "gamesGameId": 73, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 73, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 74, "anagramsQuestionText": "A SOLDIER", "anagramsAnswerText": "I REAL SOD", "gamesGameId": 74, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 74, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 1, "modesModeDescription": "Beginner", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.9, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 75, "anagramsQuestionText": "BOOBY TRAP", "anagramsAnswerText": "POOR TABBY", "gamesGameId": 75, "gamesModeId": 1, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 75, "anagramsMaxScore": 1000 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 76, "anagramsQuestionText": "CLINT EASTWOOD", "anagramsAnswerText": "OLD WEST ACTION", "gamesGameId": 76, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 76, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 77, "anagramsQuestionText": "A TELEPHONE GIRL", "anagramsAnswerText": "REPEATING HELLO", "gamesGameId": 77, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 77, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 78, "anagramsQuestionText": "WESTERN UNION", "anagramsAnswerText": "NO WIRE UNSENT", "gamesGameId": 78, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 78, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 79, "anagramsQuestionText": "ASTRONOMERS", "anagramsAnswerText": "MOON STARERS", "gamesGameId": 79, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 79, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 80, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE CENTENARIANS", "anagramsAnswerText": "I CAN HEAR TEN TENS", "gamesGameId": 80, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 80, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 81, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE MORSE CODE", "anagramsAnswerText": "HERE COME DOTS", "gamesGameId": 81, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 81, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 82, "anagramsQuestionText": "CLOTHESPINS", "anagramsAnswerText": "SO LETS PINCH", "gamesGameId": 82, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 82, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 83, "anagramsQuestionText": "MACDONALDS", "anagramsAnswerText": "CLAM AND SOD", "gamesGameId": 83, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 83, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 84, "anagramsQuestionText": "ANIMOSITY", "anagramsAnswerText": "IS NO AMITY", "gamesGameId": 84, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 84, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 85, "anagramsQuestionText": "FUNERAL", "anagramsAnswerText": "REAL FUN", "gamesGameId": 85, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 85, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 86, "anagramsQuestionText": "SUNSHINE AND SHADOW", "anagramsAnswerText": "SHOW IN SUN AND SHADE", "gamesGameId": 86, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 86, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 87, "anagramsQuestionText": "SNOOZE ALARMS", "anagramsAnswerText": "ALAS NO MORE Z S", "gamesGameId": 87, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 87, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 88, "anagramsQuestionText": "VACATION TIME", "anagramsAnswerText": "I AM NOT ACTIVE", "gamesGameId": 88, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 88, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 89, "anagramsQuestionText": "METATHESIS", "anagramsAnswerText": "ITS THE SAME", "gamesGameId": 89, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 89, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 90, "anagramsQuestionText": "SYCOPHANT", "anagramsAnswerText": "ACTS PHONY", "gamesGameId": 90, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 90, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 91, "anagramsQuestionText": "ALEC GUINNESS", "anagramsAnswerText": "GENUINE CLASS", "gamesGameId": 91, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 91, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 92, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE HOSPITAL AMBULANCE", "anagramsAnswerText": "A CAB I HUSTLE TO HELP MAN", "gamesGameId": 92, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 92, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 93, "anagramsQuestionText": "A GENTLEMAN", "anagramsAnswerText": "ELEGANT MAN", "gamesGameId": 93, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 93, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 94, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE PUBLIC ART GALLERIES", "anagramsAnswerText": "LARGE PICTURE HALLS I BET", "gamesGameId": 94, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 94, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 95, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE EARTHQUAKES", "anagramsAnswerText": "THAT QUEER SHAKE", "gamesGameId": 95, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 95, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 96, "anagramsQuestionText": "SALMAN RUSHDIE", "anagramsAnswerText": "READ SHUN ISLAM", "gamesGameId": 96, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 96, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 97, "anagramsQuestionText": "STATUE OF LIBERTY", "anagramsAnswerText": "BUILT TO STAY FREE", "gamesGameId": 97, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 97, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 98, "anagramsQuestionText": "PATRICK STEWART", "anagramsAnswerText": "A CRAP TREK TWIST", "gamesGameId": 98, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 98, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 99, "anagramsQuestionText": "INDOMITABLENESS", "anagramsAnswerText": "ENDLESS AMBITION", "gamesGameId": 99, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 99, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 100, "anagramsQuestionText": "NEW YORK TIMES", "anagramsAnswerText": "MONKEY WRITES", "gamesGameId": 100, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 100, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 101, "anagramsQuestionText": "TELEVISION PROGRAMMING", "anagramsAnswerText": "PERMEATING LIVING ROOMS", "gamesGameId": 101, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 101, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 102, "anagramsQuestionText": "DAVID LETTERMAN", "anagramsAnswerText": "NERD AMID LATE TV", "gamesGameId": 102, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 102, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 103, "anagramsQuestionText": "RUSSIAN REVOLUTION", "anagramsAnswerText": "NO EVIL RUINOUS TSAR", "gamesGameId": 103, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 103, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 104, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE COUGAR", "anagramsAnswerText": "OR HUGE CAT", "gamesGameId": 104, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 104, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 105, "anagramsQuestionText": "SPERMICIDE", "anagramsAnswerText": "I CRIMP SEED", "gamesGameId": 105, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 105, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 106, "anagramsQuestionText": "PROGERIA", "anagramsAnswerText": "PRIOR AGE", "gamesGameId": 106, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 106, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 107, "anagramsQuestionText": "GOD IS EVERYWHERE", "anagramsAnswerText": "WORD GIVER, HE EYES!", "gamesGameId": 107, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 107, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 108, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE VIDEO CAMERA", "anagramsAnswerText": "A HOME ART DEVICE", "gamesGameId": 108, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 108, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 109, "anagramsQuestionText": "GENERALISSIMO", "anagramsAnswerText": "LEGIONS ARMIES", "gamesGameId": 109, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 109, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 110, "anagramsQuestionText": "SPANISH SENORITA", "anagramsAnswerText": "SHES NOT PARISIAN", "gamesGameId": 110, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 110, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 111, "anagramsQuestionText": "CARTE BLANCHE", "anagramsAnswerText": "CANCEL THE BAR", "gamesGameId": 111, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 111, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 112, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE GAMBINO FAMILY", "anagramsAnswerText": "MIGHT BE MAFIA ONLY", "gamesGameId": 112, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 112, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 113, "anagramsQuestionText": "ARCTIC EXPEDITION", "anagramsAnswerText": "AN EXOTIC ICED TRIP", "gamesGameId": 113, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 113, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 114, "anagramsQuestionText": "RIOTS IN FRENCH CAPITAL", "anagramsAnswerText": "CONFLICT IN PARIS HEART", "gamesGameId": 114, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 114, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 115, "anagramsQuestionText": "ACTOR LOUIS DE FUNES", "anagramsAnswerText": "FATUOUS SCREEN-IDOL", "gamesGameId": 115, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 115, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 116, "anagramsQuestionText": "A SORE THROAT", "anagramsAnswerText": "ORATORS HATE", "gamesGameId": 116, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 116, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 117, "anagramsQuestionText": "SCUM OF THE EARTH", "anagramsAnswerText": "TERM OF SUCH HATE", "gamesGameId": 117, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 117, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 118, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE ACTRESS MERYL STREEP", "anagramsAnswerText": "RESPECT HER MASTER STYLE", "gamesGameId": 118, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 118, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 119, "anagramsQuestionText": "HYUNDAI ENTOURAGE", "anagramsAnswerText": "GENUINE HARDY AUTO", "gamesGameId": 119, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 119, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 120, "anagramsQuestionText": "A NIGHT TO REMEMBER", "anagramsAnswerText": "THE BIG RARE MOMENT", "gamesGameId": 120, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 120, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 121, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE SPIRIT BOARD", "anagramsAnswerText": "PROHIBITED ARTS", "gamesGameId": 121, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 121, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 122, "anagramsQuestionText": "MIDDLE EASTERN NATIONS", "anagramsAnswerText": "NESTED IN MAD RELATIONS", "gamesGameId": 122, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 122, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 123, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE APPLE MACINTOSH", "anagramsAnswerText": "MACHINES APT TO HELP", "gamesGameId": 123, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 123, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 124, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE PROFESSIONAL DANCERS", "anagramsAnswerText": "SHARE FLOOR AND NICE STEPS", "gamesGameId": 124, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 124, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 125, "anagramsQuestionText": "CAPTAIN NEMO", "anagramsAnswerText": "OCEAN PIT MAN", "gamesGameId": 125, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 125, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 126, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE LITTLE GREEN ALIENS", "anagramsAnswerText": "REAL INTELLIGENT THESE", "gamesGameId": 126, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 126, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 127, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE ERECTION", "anagramsAnswerText": "TO ENTICE HER", "gamesGameId": 127, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 127, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 128, "anagramsQuestionText": "COMPENSATION", "anagramsAnswerText": "ON PAST INCOME", "gamesGameId": 128, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 128, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 129, "anagramsQuestionText": "EATING KOSHER", "anagramsAnswerText": "SEEKING TORAH", "gamesGameId": 129, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 129, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 130, "anagramsQuestionText": "HIDEOUS MAN", "anagramsAnswerText": "IN MADHOUSE", "gamesGameId": 130, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 130, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 131, "anagramsQuestionText": "SIAD BARRE", "anagramsAnswerText": "ARAB IS RED", "gamesGameId": 131, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 131, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 132, "anagramsQuestionText": "BEAUTIFUL WOMAN", "anagramsAnswerText": "BUT I AM AWFUL ONE", "gamesGameId": 132, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 132, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 133, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE EBOLA VIRUSES", "anagramsAnswerText": "THOSE ABUSE LIVER", "gamesGameId": 133, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 133, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 134, "anagramsQuestionText": "NORIEGA", "anagramsAnswerText": "I AN OGRE", "gamesGameId": 134, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 134, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 135, "anagramsQuestionText": "VERY NICE", "anagramsAnswerText": "EVEN I CRY", "gamesGameId": 135, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 135, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 136, "anagramsQuestionText": "DISDAIN", "anagramsAnswerText": "DID A SIN", "gamesGameId": 136, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 136, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 137, "anagramsQuestionText": "EXPERIMENTATIONS", "anagramsAnswerText": "EXAM ENTIRE POINTS", "gamesGameId": 137, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 137, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 138, "anagramsQuestionText": "SPONTANEOUS", "anagramsAnswerText": "PUT NO SEASON", "gamesGameId": 138, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 138, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 139, "anagramsQuestionText": "ALEXANDER THE GREAT", "anagramsAnswerText": "DARE THAT EX GENERAL", "gamesGameId": 139, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 139, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 140, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE FEMALE ORGASMS", "anagramsAnswerText": "HER MOST FALSE GAME", "gamesGameId": 140, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 140, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 141, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE PROSTATE GLAND", "anagramsAnswerText": "THAT SPOT ENLARGED", "gamesGameId": 141, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 141, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 142, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE VERTIGOES", "anagramsAnswerText": "GO HIT EVEREST", "gamesGameId": 142, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 142, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 143, "anagramsQuestionText": "SPIDER BIOFUEL", "anagramsAnswerText": "I DO LIFE SUPERB", "gamesGameId": 143, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 143, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 144, "anagramsQuestionText": "WEEK ASHORE", "anagramsAnswerText": "HERE WE SOAK", "gamesGameId": 144, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 144, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 145, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE MACARONI", "anagramsAnswerText": "ETHNIC AROMA", "gamesGameId": 145, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 145, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 146, "anagramsQuestionText": "LINDSAY DEE LOHAN", "anagramsAnswerText": "LADY ON HEADLINES", "gamesGameId": 146, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 146, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 147, "anagramsQuestionText": "NICE SELFPORTRAIT", "anagramsAnswerText": "PERFECT ART IN OILS", "gamesGameId": 147, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 147, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 148, "anagramsQuestionText": "NICE RESTAURANT", "anagramsAnswerText": "A RAREST CUTE INN", "gamesGameId": 148, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 148, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 149, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE SPERM DONORS", "anagramsAnswerText": "MOTHERS RESPOND", "gamesGameId": 149, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 149, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 2, "modesModeDescription": "Intermediate", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.75, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 150, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE MODERN CITY", "anagramsAnswerText": "OH DIRTY CEMENT", "gamesGameId": 150, "gamesModeId": 2, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 150, "anagramsMaxScore": 1500 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 151, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE COUNTRY SIDE", "anagramsAnswerText": "NO CITY DUST HERE", "gamesGameId": 151, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 151, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 152, "anagramsQuestionText": "I RUN TO ESCAPE", "anagramsAnswerText": "A PERSECUTION", "gamesGameId": 152, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 152, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 153, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE MEANING OF LIFE", "anagramsAnswerText": "THE FINE GAME OF NIL", "gamesGameId": 153, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 153, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 154, "anagramsQuestionText": "MR MOJO RISIN", "anagramsAnswerText": "JIM MORRISON", "gamesGameId": 154, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 154, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 155, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE GREAT NEW YORK RAPID TRANSIT TUNNEL", "anagramsAnswerText": "GIANT WORK IN STREET PARTLY UNDERNEATH", "gamesGameId": 155, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 155, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 156, "anagramsQuestionText": "FLORENCE NIGHTINGALE", "anagramsAnswerText": "FLIT ON CHEERING ANGEL", "gamesGameId": 156, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 156, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 1, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 1", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 157, "anagramsQuestionText": "DARLING I LOVE YOU", "anagramsAnswerText": "AVOIDING OUR YELL", "gamesGameId": 157, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 1, "anagramsAnagramsId": 157, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 158, "anagramsQuestionText": "HEAVY RAIN", "anagramsAnswerText": "HIRE A NAVY", "gamesGameId": 158, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 158, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 159, "anagramsQuestionText": "PROTECTIONISM", "anagramsAnswerText": "CITE NO IMPORTS", "gamesGameId": 159, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 159, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 160, "anagramsQuestionText": "A DOMESTICATED ANIMAL", "anagramsAnswerText": "DOCILE AS A MAN TAMED IT", "gamesGameId": 160, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 160, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 161, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE RAILROAD TRAIN", "anagramsAnswerText": "HI I RATTLE AND ROAR", "gamesGameId": 161, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 161, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 162, "anagramsQuestionText": "A ROLLING STONE GATHERS NO MOSS", "anagramsAnswerText": "STROLLER ON GO AMASSES NOTHING", "gamesGameId": 162, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 162, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 163, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE UNITED STATES BUREAU OF FISHERIES", "anagramsAnswerText": "I RAISE THE BASS TO FEED US IN THE FUTURE", "gamesGameId": 163, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 163, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 2, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 2", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 164, "anagramsQuestionText": "CHRISTMAS TREE", "anagramsAnswerText": "SEARCH SET TRIM", "gamesGameId": 164, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 2, "anagramsAnagramsId": 164, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 165, "anagramsQuestionText": "STUDENT INFORMATION PROCESSING BOARD", "anagramsAnswerText": "COMPUTATION TRANSGRESSION FORBIDDEN", "gamesGameId": 165, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 165, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 166, "anagramsQuestionText": "HOWARD STERN", "anagramsAnswerText": "RETARD SHOWN", "gamesGameId": 166, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 166, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 167, "anagramsQuestionText": "EGALITARIAN", "anagramsAnswerText": "ANTI REGALIA", "gamesGameId": 167, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 167, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 168, "anagramsQuestionText": "SINGER MARIA CALLAS", "anagramsAnswerText": "ALL SCREAMING ARIAS", "gamesGameId": 168, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 168, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 169, "anagramsQuestionText": "SIR STANLEY MATTHEWS", "anagramsAnswerText": "MEANS STAR WITH STYLE", "gamesGameId": 169, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 169, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 170, "anagramsQuestionText": "CRIME NOVELIST", "anagramsAnswerText": "TRIMS VIOLENCE", "gamesGameId": 170, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 170, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 3, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 3", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 171, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE PORNOGRAPHIC WEBSITES", "anagramsAnswerText": "ITS HER BORING PEEP SHOW ACT", "gamesGameId": 171, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 3, "anagramsAnagramsId": 171, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 172, "anagramsQuestionText": "ACTOR SYLVESTER STALLONE", "anagramsAnswerText": "VERY COOL TALENTLESS STAR", "gamesGameId": 172, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 172, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 173, "anagramsQuestionText": "MISS SERENA WILLIAMS", "anagramsAnswerText": "WIN SLAM SMILE ARISES", "gamesGameId": 173, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 173, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 174, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE COSTA BRAVA REGION OF SPAIN", "anagramsAnswerText": "ANCHORING OF PRIVATE SEA BOATS", "gamesGameId": 174, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 174, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 175, "anagramsQuestionText": "SIR LANCELOT AND GUINEVERE", "anagramsAnswerText": "INTRIGUES CAN END REAL LOVE", "gamesGameId": 175, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 175, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 176, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE GROUP GUNS N ROSES", "anagramsAnswerText": "OGRE RUNS UP THE SONGS", "gamesGameId": 176, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 176, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 177, "anagramsQuestionText": "HEBREW UNIVERSITY OF JERUSALEM", "anagramsAnswerText": "SURE OUR VERY ABLE JEWISH MEN FIT", "gamesGameId": 177, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 177, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 178, "anagramsQuestionText": "TO CAST PEARLS BEFORE SWINE", "anagramsAnswerText": "CAN REFER TO POSSIBLE WASTE", "gamesGameId": 178, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 178, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 4, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 4", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 179, "anagramsQuestionText": "SINGER BILLY OCEAN", "anagramsAnswerText": "REALLY SONIC BEING", "gamesGameId": 179, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 4, "anagramsAnagramsId": 179, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 180, "anagramsQuestionText": "PAINTER MICHELANGELO BUONARROTI", "anagramsAnswerText": "HEART INTO MARBLE OR UPON A CEILING", "gamesGameId": 180, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 180, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 181, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE AFTERMATH OF KATRINA", "anagramsAnswerText": "TAKE THAT HAT OFF MARINER", "gamesGameId": 181, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 181, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 182, "anagramsQuestionText": "AND THEY LIVED HAPPILY EVER AFTER", "anagramsAnswerText": "DELIVERED THAT VERY HAPPY FINALE", "gamesGameId": 182, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 182, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 183, "anagramsQuestionText": "MOTION PICTURE A BEAUTIFUL MIND", "anagramsAnswerText": "DELIRIUM BUT A FINE COMPUTATION", "gamesGameId": 183, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 183, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 184, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE FAMOUS ANIMATOR WALT DISNEY", "anagramsAnswerText": "AUTHOR OF TINY SWEET MAD ANIMALS", "gamesGameId": 184, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 184, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 185, "anagramsQuestionText": "ACTRESS SIENNA ROSE MILLER", "anagramsAnswerText": "STAR IN LESSER CINEMA ROLES", "gamesGameId": 185, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 185, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 5, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 5", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 186, "anagramsQuestionText": "CHRISTIANS, MUSLIMS AND THE JEWS", "anagramsAnswerText": "JERUSALEM STANDS WITHIN SCHISM", "gamesGameId": 186, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 5, "anagramsAnagramsId": 186, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 187, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE SINGER LITTLE RICHARD", "anagramsAnswerText": "RECREATED THRILLING HITS", "gamesGameId": 187, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 187, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 188, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE GOLDEN GLOBE AWARDS CEREMONIAL", "anagramsAnswerText": "OTHER ADORABLE CINEMA LEGENDS GLOW", "gamesGameId": 188, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 188, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 189, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA GEORGE WALKER BUSH", "anagramsAnswerText": "A GANGSTER FROM THE WHITE HOUSE UNDERTAKES DEBATE FREE POLITICS", "gamesGameId": 189, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 189, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 190, "anagramsQuestionText": "WILLIAM HENRY GATES", "anagramsAnswerText": "MY WEALTH IS IN LARGE", "gamesGameId": 190, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 190, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 191, "anagramsQuestionText": "MADONNA LOUISE CICCONE", "anagramsAnswerText": "NICE MUSIC AND A COOL ONE", "gamesGameId": 191, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 191, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 192, "anagramsQuestionText": "LOVE AND EROTICISM", "anagramsAnswerText": "NO MORE CIVIL DATES", "gamesGameId": 192, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 192, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 193, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE WALT DISNEY PARKS", "anagramsAnswerText": "WEALTHY PARENTS KIDS", "gamesGameId": 193, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 193, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 6, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 6", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 194, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE FILM ACTRESS SOPHIA LOREN", "anagramsAnswerText": "OH SHE A PERFECT MILLIONS STAR", "gamesGameId": 194, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 6, "anagramsAnagramsId": 194, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 195, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE ARHYTHMIAS", "anagramsAnswerText": "HAH ITS MY HEART", "gamesGameId": 195, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 195, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 196, "anagramsQuestionText": "ACTRESS UMA THURMAN", "anagramsAnswerText": "HUMAN TRUSTS CAMERA", "gamesGameId": 196, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 196, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 197, "anagramsQuestionText": "BUSH ADMINISTRATION", "anagramsAnswerText": "IS BRUTISH DAMNATION", "gamesGameId": 197, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 197, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 198, "anagramsQuestionText": "ADOLF HITLER AND EVA BRAUN", "anagramsAnswerText": "BLOND FRAU HAD AN EVIL RAT", "gamesGameId": 198, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 198, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 199, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE LIVE EARTH CONCERTS", "anagramsAnswerText": "RECENT VOCAL HITS THERE", "gamesGameId": 199, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 199, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 200, "anagramsQuestionText": "MODEL PARIS HILTON", "anagramsAnswerText": "POOR MIND IS LETHAL", "gamesGameId": 200, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 200, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 7, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 7", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 201, "anagramsQuestionText": "FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF GERMANY", "anagramsAnswerText": "FRIENDLY PLACE FOR A BEER MUG", "gamesGameId": 201, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 7, "anagramsAnagramsId": 201, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 202, "anagramsQuestionText": "MICHAEL PRAETORIUS", "anagramsAnswerText": "I HEAR REAL TOP MUSIC", "gamesGameId": 202, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 202, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 203, "anagramsQuestionText": "FREE ONLINE DATING SERVICE", "anagramsAnswerText": "EASIER LOVE FINDING CENTER", "gamesGameId": 203, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 203, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 204, "anagramsQuestionText": "GREAT WHEEL OF CHINA", "anagramsAnswerText": "NOW FACE REAL HEIGHT", "gamesGameId": 204, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 204, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 205, "anagramsQuestionText": "CHARLIE AND THE CHOCOLATE FACTORY", "anagramsAnswerText": "THE CHILDREN EACH TRY A LOT OF CACAO", "gamesGameId": 205, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 205, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 206, "anagramsQuestionText": "GWEN RENEE STEFANI", "anagramsAnswerText": "A FINE N SWEET GENRE", "gamesGameId": 206, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 206, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 207, "anagramsQuestionText": "OPRAH WINFREY NETWORK", "anagramsAnswerText": "RATIFY HER KNOWN POWER", "gamesGameId": 207, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 207, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 8, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 8", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 208, "anagramsQuestionText": "ROLLING STONES BAND", "anagramsAnswerText": "REAL NOT BLIND SONGS", "gamesGameId": 208, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 8, "anagramsAnagramsId": 208, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 209, "anagramsQuestionText": "A PIONEER NEUROLOGIST SIGMUND FREUD", "anagramsAnswerText": "GRIP GENUINE RUDE SOLUTION OF DREAMS", "gamesGameId": 209, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 209, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 210, "anagramsQuestionText": "BRUCE SPRINGSTEEN", "anagramsAnswerText": "CREEP BRINGS TUNES", "gamesGameId": 210, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 210, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 211, "anagramsQuestionText": "GOLDILOCKS AND THE THREE BEARS", "anagramsAnswerText": "HER SNACK GOOD AS HER LITTLE BED", "gamesGameId": 211, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 211, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 212, "anagramsQuestionText": "CABERNET SAUVIGNON", "anagramsAnswerText": "CONSENT IN VAGUE BAR", "gamesGameId": 212, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 212, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 213, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE LATEX CONDOMS", "anagramsAnswerText": "MAN CLOTHED TO SEX", "gamesGameId": 213, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 213, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 214, "anagramsQuestionText": "MISS MILEY CYRUS", "anagramsAnswerText": "MY MUSE IS LYRICS", "gamesGameId": 214, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 214, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 9, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 9", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 215, "anagramsQuestionText": "ELISHA GRAVES OTIS", "anagramsAnswerText": "HIS ELEVATOR IS GAS", "gamesGameId": 215, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 9, "anagramsAnagramsId": 215, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 216, "anagramsQuestionText": "SINGER DIANA ROSS", "anagramsAnswerText": "DEAR AIRS IN SONGS", "gamesGameId": 216, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 216, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 217, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE MOST BEAUTIFUL GIRL IN THE WORLD", "anagramsAnswerText": "O HIS TRUE DELIGHTFUL BRITTLE WOMAN", "gamesGameId": 217, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 217, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 218, "anagramsQuestionText": "ROME WAS NOT BUILT IN A DAY", "anagramsAnswerText": "TOWN MADE BY OUR ITALIANS", "gamesGameId": 218, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 218, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 219, "anagramsQuestionText": "OLD STORY OF LOVE TRIANGLE", "anagramsAnswerText": "DISLOYAL LOVER FORGOTTEN", "gamesGameId": 219, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 219, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 220, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE LAST FASHION", "anagramsAnswerText": "THAT IS ON A FLESH", "gamesGameId": 220, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 220, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 221, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE WINTER OLYMPIC GAMES", "anagramsAnswerText": "MEN TRY WHITE MAGIC SLOPE", "gamesGameId": 221, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 221, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 222, "anagramsQuestionText": "METRO GOLDWYN MAYER", "anagramsAnswerText": "WANTED MEMORY GLORY", "gamesGameId": 222, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 222, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 223, "anagramsQuestionText": "THE SINGLE EUROPEAN CURRENCY", "anagramsAnswerText": "THEY CANCEL GREEN IN OUR PURSE", "gamesGameId": 223, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 223, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 224, "anagramsQuestionText": "WINDOWS MEDIA PLAYER", "anagramsAnswerText": "WE AIM WONDER DISPLAY", "gamesGameId": 224, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 224, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 },
 { "modesModeId": 3, "modesModeDescription": "Advanced", "modesHintsPercentile": 0.5, "levelsLevelId": 10, "levelsLevelDescription": "Level 10", "categoriesCategoryId": 1, "categoriesCategoryDescription": "General", "anagramsAnagramId": 225, "anagramsQuestionText": "MARRIAGE COUNSELING", "anagramsAnswerText": " CLEANING OUR MIRAGES", "gamesGameId": 225, "gamesModeId": 3, "gamesLevelId": 10, "anagramsAnagramsId": 225, "anagramsMaxScore": 2000 }]